

var questions = [{
        id: '13',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'How punctual are you? Honestly.',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'I take pride in always being on time.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'I’m mostly on time.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'I’m always running late, but I always have a good excuse.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Other...'}]
    }, {
        id: '12',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'How much do you value punctuality?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'I expect others to be exactly on time.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'Somewhat, as long as it’s under 5 minutes.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'I don’t mind if someone’s late as long as they tell me on time.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'I’m quite flexible about it.'}]
    }, {
        id: '11',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'Do you enjoy working under a project manager?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'Usually yes.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'No, they are mostly useless.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'I never had a project manager.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Other...'}]
    }, {
        id: '10',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'What do you find the most annoying thing about working in an office?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'That I have to be on time.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'I get distracted by the crowd.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'Sitting at the same desk all day.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Other...'}]
    }, {
        id: '9',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'How would you go about solving an incredibly hard problem?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'I’d put in hours and work as hard as I can.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'I’d find someone who could tell me (part of) the solution.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'I would hire a freelancer to get it done for me.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Other...'}]
    }, {
        id: '8',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'Would you be willing to work part time?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'Full time is what I prefer.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'I don’t want to have fixed hours.'}, {id: 2, answer: '2-3 days a week is fine.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Other...'}]
    }, {
        id: '7',
        type: 'text-only',
        question: 'What types of job would you consider?'
    }, {
        id: '6',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'Why would you like to have a new job?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'I’m bored at my current job.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'I’m a fresh graduate.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'I want something more challenging.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Other...'}]
    }, {
        id: '5',
        type: 'text-only',
        question: 'How many jobs have you applied for this year?'
    }, {
        id: '4',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'What is the most important factor in finding your next job?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'Getting a high salary'}, {id: 1, answer: 'Learning as much as possible.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'Having fun with my colleagues.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Other...'}]
    }, {
        id: '3',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'What are your thoughts on remote work?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'Yes, I hate sitting in the same office every day.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'I would prefer having an office, but it’s not necessary.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'I find myself most productive in the office.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Other'}]
    }, {
        id: '2',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'How much do you wanna focus on solving a specific problem at work?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'I’d like to dedicate my full attention to solving a single problem really well.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'I’d like to work on multiple problems simultaneously.'}, {id: 2, answer: 'Other.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'Not sure.'}]
    }, {
        id: '1',
        type: 'multiple-choice',
        question: 'What’s the ideal office size you would like to have?',
        answers: [{id: 0, answer: 'I want us to all fit around a table.'}, {id: 1, answer: 'Smaller startup (10-20).'}, {id: 2, answer: 'Medium-sized.'}, {id: 3, answer: 'I would like to work for a long-established, big company (300+).'}]
}];


module.exports = questions;

